<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">ArabPlast</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_exhibitions">Exhibitions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_expo">AboutExpo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">MainMenu</string>
    <string name="toMainMenu">To main menu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ivent_info">IventInfo</string>
    <string name="ChooseExhibition">Choose Exhibition:</string>
    <string name="ArabPlast2015">"  <b>ArabPlast 2015"</b>\n\u0020 10 – 13 Jan 2015"</string>
    <string name="Login">" Login"</string>
    <string name="AllExhibitions">" All Exhibitions"</string>
    <string name="AboutExpo">" About Expo"</string>
    <string name="ExhibitorCatalogue">" Exhibitor Catalogue"</string>
    <string name="ProductCatalogue">" Product Catalogue"</string>
    <string name="FloorPlan">" Floor Plan"</string>
    <string name="Visitors">" Visitors"</string>
    <string name="TravelInfo">" Travel Info"</string>
    <string name="Contacts">" Contacts"</string>
    <string name="AboutApp">" About App"</string>
    <string name="WelcomeToArabPlast2015">        Welcome to ArabPlast 2015!\n
        Now is the time to expand the borders of your business…\n
        Now is the time to push your sales…\n
        Now is the time to build your brand image…\n
        Now is the time to showcase your products and services…\n
        Now is the time to mark your 2015 calendar…\n
        Unveiling the LARGEST plastics, petrochemicals and rubber industry trade show in MENA region –
        ARABPLAST 2015 - the FASTEST way to enter the vast MENA region’s plastics, petrochemicals and rubber industry.
        ArabPlast 2015 is envisioned to make better business sense to the participants who are giving shape to a better world.
        The captains of the plastics and rubber industry would be here to unveil products solutions, cutting-edge technology,
        and revolutionary innovations and forge international alliances. Yes, it’s an event that would provide a greater leverage
        to international exhibitors and trade visitors with decision-making authority. Seize this opportunity as a manufacturer or
        service provider at ArabPlast 2015. It’s the perfect venue to showcase your products and innovations, develop contacts and
        sign profitable partnerships.</string>
    <string name="WhyVisit" formatted="false">        Investments in plastics and petrochemical sector is on the upswing
        defying the global financial crisis. The Gulf petrochemicals industry continues to be
        the world’s largest producer and exporter, offloading the majority of its output
        to more than 150 countries worldwide.The Gulf states account for 11% of the $600BN global petrochemical industry.
        Over the next five years, the Gulf’s market share of the global petrochemical industry will jump to over 17%,
        according to an industrial study. GCC plastics industry becoming more vibrant as the vibrant as the demand
        for the new products is growing with rapid speed in the region.</string>
    <string name="WhyVisit2" formatted="false">        Gulf states are poised to become the world’s largest source of polyethylene (PE) and polypropylene (PP).
        The PE production capacities in the GCC countries are expected to increase from 10.7 million tonnes in 2009
        to 21.5 million tonnes by 2015, while the production of PP is expected to rise from 4.8 million tonnes in 2009
        to 9.5 million tonnes by 2015. This will bring the combined production capacities of the two major polyolefin resins to
        over 31 million tonnes by 2015. By 2020, GCC plastic consumption will grow about 8%,compared to 25 % by Europe and NAFTA countries,
        and 37 % in Asian and Oceanic countries. The world will consume 540 million tonnes of plastic in 2020,
        The plastic sector also benefiting strongly from Gulf Countries drive towards “green buildings” in the recent years.
        There is continuous growth in the plastics converting industry with substantial expansion of polymer production in the Middle East.
        This makes the region a major market for plastic additives. The UAE’s massive drive to build one of the world’s most advanced
        infrastructures has fuelled demand for plastics products, from tubes to cables and wires. The automotive industry benefits
        from the use of plastic tubes because the material makes cars lighter; so do hospitals are shifting from breakable glass syringes
        to plastic ones.</string>
    <string name="WhyExhibit1" formatted="false">        Arabplast 2013 grew 34% following greater response from exhibitors and sponsors.
        Arabplast is also ranked as No. 1 show in the region for plastics, petrochemicals and rubber industry.
        A record number of 794 companies from 41 countries have participated in Arabplast 2013.
        On display at Arabplast 2013 there were new products and technologies in inj ection moulding, blow moulding,
        wrapping and packaging, pre and post plastic processing techniques as well as raw materials, such as additives and polymers.
        The show covered a wide spectrum of plastic machinery, plastic/rubber processing technology, pre and post-processing systems,
        plastic packaging technology, injection moulding, blow moulding, wrapping technology, extrusions, chemicals and additives,
        semi finished goods, engineering plastics and plastic products.Positive visitor response to high International level
        of participation and wide spectrum of exhibits.
        Approximately 33% more trade professionals came to Arabplast 2013 edition. 39% came from countries outside of GCC.
        The largest number of foreign visitors came from Saudi Arabia, Oman, Qatar, Bahrain, Kuwait, Iran, Pakistan, Egypt,
        African countries, and India, while China, Germany, Jordan, Syria, and Lebanon contributed adequately to the trade visitors.
        The number of foreign visitors from the Saudi Arabia, Oman, Kuwait, Qatar, Iran , Lebanon, and Jordan the other important
        foreign markets for exhibiting companies manufacturers, rose to 36% on an average basis, as compared to last edition of Arabplast.
        49% of the trade visitors showed their interest for Plastic machinery and Plastic related equipments, while some 31% of the visitors
        expressed their interest for raw materials, and 20% of trade visitors were interested to meet participants
        from Thermoforming, Extruders, Packaging related companies. 67 percent of the visitors are employed as high-level management.
        33% of ArabPlast visitors indicated that they were influential in making their company’s investment decisions.</string>
    <string name="WhyExhibitPrices" formatted="false"><b>BASIC PACKAGE</b> 4MX3M(ONE SIDE OPEN)  - US$ 455/-PER SQM (MINIMUM OF 12 SQM)
    REAR AND WALLS (WHITE OCTANORM PANEL)
    FASCIA NAME IN ENGLISH
    CARPET TILES BLUE and GREY
    ONE 13AMP 220V PLUG SOCKETOne NEWLINE TABLE
    2 CHAIRS
    3 SPOTLIGHTS
\n
\n <b>SUPERIOR PACKAGE</b> 4MX3M(ONE SIDE OPEN) - US$ 475/-PER SQM (MINIMUM OF 12 SQM)
    WOODEN ROUND BOOTH DIVIDERS WITH ORGANIZERS LOGO/NAME
    NORMAL OCTANORM FASCIA
    WOODEN DIVIDER ACCENT IN TRI-COLOR FOR TROPHY LOOK EFFECT
    NORMAL OCTANORM WALL WITH WHITE PANEL
    FOLDING DOOR FOR STORE ROOM
    NEWLINE NORMAL COUNTER FOR RECEPTION
    ROUND TABLE WITH 2 GRAY LEATHER CHAIR
    ONE 13AMP, 220V PLUG SOCKET
    4 SPOTLIGHTS
    FLOOR CARPET
    ONE POTTED PLANT
\n
\n <b>SPACE ONLY</b> - US$ 420/-PER SQM (MINIMUM OF 36 SQM)
    PLEASE NOTE SPACE ONLY EXHIBITORS SHOULD ORDER SEPARATE POWER/ELECTRICITY CONNECTION FOR THEIR STAND AREA.
    SERVICES COMMON TO BASIC,SUPERIOR and SPACE ONLY
    GENERAL ILLUMINATION
    GENERAL SECURITY SERVICES
    TECHNICAL AND ORGANIZATIONAL SERVICES
    ENTRY IN THE OFFICIAL CATALOGUE
    USE OF THE PRESS OFFICE</string>
    <string name="numberVisitors"><b>25 646</b>\n Visitors"</string>
    <string name="numberExhibitors"><b>794</b>\nExhibitors</string>
    <string name="squareMeters"><b>40 000</b>\nSquare meters</string>
    <string name="numberOfCountries"><b>41</b>\nCountries</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="Mr.JeenJoshuaExhibitionManager"><b>" Mr. Jeen Joshua</b>\n Exhibition Manager"</string>
    <string name="alfajerAddress">Al Fajer Information &amp; Services P.O. Box\n11183, Dubai, United Arab Emirates</string>

</resources>
